Oleg Ryakhovsky

E-mail: <u>oleg.ryakhovsky@gmail.com</u>

2326wz@gmail.com

Phone: +7 915 483 08 10

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/2326wz/

GitHub: https://github.com/2326wz

PROFILE

Deal with Deep Learning, Computer Vision and Machine learning over one year. Started carrier as Telecommunications engineer, worked a lot with statistics of cellular networks, then came to data analysis and development area.

Interested in future development as a Data Scientist, preferably in fields of Computer Vision or Big Data Analysis.

Addicted to ml4sg ideas, collaborate at Lacmus DL project https://lacmus-foundation.github.io/.

PROJECTS

1. "Sharp-In": Deep learning solution for improvement of poor quality drone images

Practically used in rescue of lost people in wild territories.

https://github.com/lacmus-foundation/sharp-in

2. Augmented dataset preparat	ion	project	s:
-------------------------------	-----	---------	----

Image Inpainting:

Bounding Boxes crop utility:

https://github.com/lacmus-foundation/lacmus/tree/master/data_utils/ImgGeneratorhttps://github.com/lacmus-foundation/lacmus/tree/master/data_utils/bboxCropper

KAGGLE

Fraud detection (ML):	https://www.kaggle.com/c/ieee-fraud-detection
Image recognition (DL):	https://www.kaggle.com/c/hotdogornot
Others:	https://www.kaggle.com/caba7005452/competitions

SKILLS

Languages:	#Python #SQL	
Libraries:	#Keras #pandas #sklearn #LGBM #Pytorch #Tensorflow #matplotlib #XGboost #CatBoost #OpenCV #numpy	

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

NOKIA NETWORKS - Automation systems developer	2018 - now
Analyzed bottlenecks and time losses in equipment delivery process. Based on analysis:	
Created an ML tool for delivery delays prediction.	
 Wrote and implemented numerous handy tools to improve efficiency of logistic staff. 	
 Developed a server based application for: a) automated collection, generation and distribution of different progress reports, b) automated sending of action reminders to process stakeholders, c) running minor scheduled processes in company's intranet. 	
 Wrote an application for running transactions in SAP to eliminate manual work. 	
As a result I'm saving to company over 5000 man-hours per year.	
HUAWEI Tech.Co - Managed Services Procurement department, leader	2014 - 2018
 Wrote applications for tenders results analysis and visualization. 	
• Improved contracts preparation process with saving apx 2 man-hours per one contract by mean of simple code.	
PromKompozit, OOO - Engineer	2013 - 2014
• Developed an application for analysis of possible angular velocity of spinning airplane based on airframe and foil parameters.	
NOKIA NETWORKS - Radio network expert	2004 2042
Projecting, analysis and optimization of 2G-3G networks	2004 – 2012
Vimpelcom, OAO - Radio network statistics engineer	
Statistical analysis and optimization of 2G networks	2002 - 2004
Ericsson Russia – Radio network engineer	2000 2002
 Projecting of 2G networks 	2000 - 2002

EDUCATION

Moscow Power Engineering Institute - Qualified as Radio Engineer	1993 - 2000	
Machine learning and Deep learning courses at ODS.ai	2019	